I don't think new posters
are gonna cut it.
What?
You're gonna need to
up your campaign game.
Well. perhaps my campaign
manager has some ideas.
You mean besides
all the e-mails I sent you?
I should
probably read those.
Nolan.
Lopez needs a unit
to accompany her this morning.
and that's you.
Yes. sir.
My pleasure.
Uh. sir...
Can I count on your vote?
I'm still doing my due diligence
with the candidates.
It's Smitty!
You got my vote.
- Thank you.
- Not mine.
I'm not in
the union yet.
Right.
Looks like we're gonna be
riding together.
Everything good?
Uh. yeah.
We have to interview one of
these Sovereign Citizen idiots.
He allegedly assaulted
an IRS agent
who had a few questions
about why Marvin Reynolds
wasn't paying
any of his taxes.
Angela. I thought we were gonna
talk more this morning.
I woke up.
you were gone.
Yeah. I have a job.
remember?
Uh...
I'll wait for you
by the shop.
I'm right behind you.
Angela.
I don't have time
for this conversation right now.
How many times
can I apologize?
I told you.
I didn't have a choice.
Look. making a deal
with Elijah
was the only way that I could
get you home safe.
I understand why you did
what you did.
I can even understand
why you kept it from me...
You don't want to stress out
the new mom.
But to tell me
I need to stay out of it
after asking
for my help...
Look. I didn't
mean for you...
I got myself into this.
No. you got us
into this.
and I'm going to
get us out.
Well. how do you plan
to do that?
By telling Elijah Stone you
don't work for him anymore.
And if he's got
a problem with that.
me and a couple hundred
of my closest friends...
No. you can't.
He has leverage on me.
He could take it
to the state bar.
I could lose
my license.
Last night. you swore
you didn't break any laws.
I haven't.
There could be
some ethical questions.
I can't do this
right now.
We'll talk tonight.
He can't really believe
he can buy votes
with water bottles.
I mean. not when I have
a real message.
a message of change.
Actually.
he's beating you.
I did some polling.
and you are
definitely behind.
I'm losing to Smitty?
Oh.
that's embarrassing.
You know what would
really help?
An endorsement from someone
respected within the department.
No. don't drag me
into this.
No. I have never endorsed
a candidate. and I never will.
Voting is a private matter.
Here. maybe this will help
wash away the taste of defeat.
This bottle's
been opened.
Oh. those bottles
are recyclable.
It's just my way of giving back
to the environment.
Where's the water from?
My bathroom sink.
Water's water.
♪ Whoa. oh. oh. oh. oh. oh.
whoa. oh. oh ♪
♪ I'm gonna win for you. like I know ♪
*THE ROOKIE*
♪ You want me to do. hey ♪
Season 04  Episode 08
Episode Title: "Hit and Run"
Aired on: December 05. 2021.
Everything okay
with you and Wesley?
- No.
- I get it.
Sarah wanted to divorce me
at least three times
during Henry's
first year.
It felt like I couldn't
get anything right.
It's rough.
those early days.
You know. it's a lack of sleep.
it's fear of the unknown.
a baby that
won't stop crying...
It's not about that.
What is it about?
Right now. it's about you
not minding your own business.
Put the shop in drive
and let's go.
I will have to
put it in reverse
before I can
actually put it...
I know that look.
No more jokes.
Genny.
Sergeant Bradford.
You look skinny.
Have you been eating?
- Every day.
- Uh-huh.
This is a restricted area.
How'd you get in here?
Oh. the guy who's
handing out waters let me in.
Okay. Yeah.
Don't drink that.
Um...
So. what are you
doing here?
I just wanted to
see my big brother.
Oh. hi.
I'm Lucy Chen.
I know that
we just met.
but if you have
any embarrassing stories
from his childhood.
that...
So you just
wanted to see me?
I didn't even know
you were in town.
So you're not just not
returning my calls.
you're also ignoring
the messages
telling you
I'm coming to town.
Because I know
why you're here.
and I've made
my position very clear.
We have to
talk about it.
Look. I gotta
get to work.
Maybe we can
have dinner tonight.
So you can
blow me off at the last minute?
No.
Why don't I do one of those
ride-along thingies?
That way. we could have
the whole day to catch up.
Yeah.
See. you gotta get permission
to do a ride-along.
It's...
It's a long process.
a ton of paperwork.
Hey. you're
a sergeant now.
You can just
approve it yourself.
Great.
Let's hit the streets.
Let's.
Did Tim have any. um.
nicknames
when he was a kid?
So. it's been
six weeks.
Any thoughts
on my progress?
I write an evaluation
every day.
Those are my thoughts
on your progress.
Right. I mean.
that's the technical stuff.
but I was just
wondering. like.
what you thought of me
as a person.
What matters is what
I think about you as a cop.
You want people to like you.
go make some friends.
Harper.
What?
Oh. no. no.
This is the first
I'm hearing about this.
He can't do that.
though. right?
Maybe?
W-What do you mean maybe?
You...
You are the lawyer.
Shouldn't you know that
for sure?
Okay. well.
I-I'ma need you
to get some damn clarity
and call me back.
- Is everything okay?
- No.
My ex-husband
is getting married.
and he wants to move
to San Francisco
and take my daughter
with him.
Can he do that?
I don't know.
This is Detective Angela Lopez.
badge number 1777.
I need complete histories.
statewide and CJIC.
for the personal
file numbers...
NWC-057. JPA-733.
BXR-389.
And if any of those queries
generate other file numbers.
can I get completes
on those. too?
Thanks.
What was that about?
Uh. another case
I'm working on.
Anything
I can help with?
No. I got it handled.
Oh. yeah. he tried to highlight
his hair right before prom.
He ended up
looking like Slim Shady.
Hm!
Oh. you know what?
I think I have a picture of it.
- Oh. my God. yes!
- Genny.
What. you'd... you'd rather
I keep this photo private?
That's fine.
Let's talk about dad.
I have nothing to say.
Okay.
What's your cellphone number?
I'll text it to you.
Genny. come on.
We don't need your distractions.
Police work
is serious stuff.
Ooh. boy.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Hey. ma'am. I'm gonna
need you to pull over.
You'll never catch me!
Have you been
drinking?
It's not illegal
to drink and bike.
Actually. it is.
The way you were swerving
in and out of traffic...
Oh. Uh...
You could have caused
an accident.
- Alright?
- I just wanna get some tacos!
Don't be such a butt.
Okay. ma'am. we can cite you
for public intoxication.
or if you don't cooperate.
we'll charge you with a DUI.
Screw you. you
Ken-doll-ass-looking mimbo...
Hey. honey.
Honey. I know
you're having a bad day.
but that doesn't give you
the right to be rude.
They're just doing
their jobs.
Why don't you take
a few deep breaths
and sit down
for a minute?
I'm sorry.
That was impressive.
I teach
fourth graders.
Oh. great.
Okay. look. you cannot move
our daughter to San Francisco.
What... What...
What are we gonna do?
Put her on a plane
every weekend?
Enroll her
in two schools?
No. obviously not.
What you are asking for
is near total custody
and I see her on weekends
and holidays. which...
Which is a violation of our
custody agreement. by the way.
- so I...
- I'm gonna need...
If you're satisfied with
your message. press one.
If you'd like to
re-record. pre...
Look. I know he's
your daughter's father.
but that man is a coward
for springing this on you.
Well. he might have
left a message last week
saying that he needed to talk
to me about something. but...
Maybe it was two messages.
There might have been
an e-mail. But...
Okay. Then. why didn't you
call him back?
I don't know. I thought
it was about something else.
Oh. so you were
avoiding him?
No. I was n...
I don't know. Maybe.
I did... I didn't want to
have to talk about...
Halloween.
What happened
on Halloween?
Ohhh.
Mm.
Sorry.
Well. we're about to land
at Marvin Reynolds' place.
What are we
hoping for?
Ideally. he admits to
assaulting the IRS agent
and we hook him up.
Otherwise. it's just
a misdemeanor
not committed
in police presence.
His word against
the IRS agent's.
Yeah. I always mix up these
Sovereign Citizen guys
with the
Posse Comitatus group.
They're all just part of
the same crazy.
anti-government soup...
All just looking for their way
not to pay their fair share.
I think there's a little
more to it than that.
Good for you.
Look. there's always
people in society
who feel like
they're on the outside.
And some are
easily manipulated.
Some are so desperate
to find a purpose
that they allow themselves
to be infected
by the most absurd
beliefs.
so much so.
they could rationalize
beating up
an IRS agent...
Or worse.
Nah.
My theory's better.
These whack jobs just believe
they're above the law.
until they need it.
There it is.
This guy have
a history of violence?
Why do you think
I'm putting on a vest?
Let me guess.
Domestic abuse?
Among other things.
but he never did any time.
Hey. get the hell off
of my property!
Sir. I'm Detective Lopez.
and this is Officer Nolan.
Are you
Marvin Reynolds?
You know what?
That name is a straw-man. okay?
I'm a free man.
I'm living upon the land.
You're representatives of
a corporate government.
You have no authority
over me.
I am not a citizen of
your corporation!
Sir. a complaint's been
filed against you
claiming you assaulted
a federal employee from the IRS.
Yeah. they're trying to
take my house.
Okay?
But. see. there's no
legitimate money.
because we went off
the gold standard in 1933.
So you're admitting
to the assault?
No. I admit nothing. okay?
And I don't... I don't...
I don't have any obligation
to submit
to your unlawful inquiry.
Sir. we need to talk to you
about what happened.
Can you please step out
onto the porch?
I'm a constitutional activist.
okay?
I know my rights.
A-A-And what you're
practicing here. it's tyranny.
Sir. we just want
your side of the story.
I promise you. this will be
much more productive
if you just step out
onto the porch.
Ah.
Yeah. that's...
That's not gonna happen.
Okay?
So get off of my property.
Now.
Sir. take it easy.
Don't do anything stupid.
Sir?
Gun!
Move. move. move!
7-Adam-15.
Shots fired at our location.
Send backup. Code 3.
You ready?
Yeah.
He's going outside.
He's running.
No!
Control. 7-Adam-15.
Code 3 traffic.
We just got 246'd
by a submachine gun.
Suspect vehicle...
Silver sedan.
last seen headed west
on Oakwood.
Suspect still armed.
Air Three
is lifting now.
I'm ten-nine-seven.
Searching for suspect's vehicle.
Control. 7-Adam-100
on scene.
Stay in the car.
Anybody hurt?
We're good. but we've got
one shooter outstanding...
Marvin Reynolds.
Suspect vehicle...
Silver sedan.
Did not get very good I.D.
I didn't get any plates.
Alright. let's pull
DMV records.
see what Marvin's
got registered.
Got to find everything
we can about this guy.
- On it.
- I'll ask for
a telephonic warrant
to search the GPS of
his vehicle on his phone.
If we can see where he's been.
it might help us know
where he's going.
Control. 7-Adam-100.
advise crime scene
they can begin processing
and start a board-up crew.
And I need all available units
for a city-wide manhunt.
Alright. listen up...
At approximately 1057 hours.
suspect Marvin Reynolds
opened fire
on Officer Nolan
and Detective Lopez
with a submachine gun.
We're dealing with
a Sovereign Citizen
who's clearly snapped.
He assaulted an IRS agent
who showed up two days ago
to start foreclosure
proceedings.
We're gonna hit up
every known address.
every relative's address.
every associate.
every friend of a friend
of a friend
until someone
coughs this guy up.
Okay. he hasn't renewed any of
his registrations in over four years.
but I got a list of everything
he's owned going back to 2005.
You got a silver Honda
on there or a Toyota?
There's a silver Civic.
as well as three other vehicles.
Alright. send that list
to everyone's boxes.
Make sure
you keep checking.
This is a very fluid
situation.
Now let's go get this guy
before he does something worse.
Phew.
What's going on?
I'm taking you back to the station.
It's too dangerous.
- Forget it.
- Genny.
I'm not leaving until
we talk about dad.
Oh. you are impossible.
I'm impossible?
Lucy. who's more difficult.
me or Tim?
Of course
she's gonna pick me!
Because you are the most
stubborn person alive.
which is. by the way.
why you're still single.
Okay.
First of all. I'm not.
- And second...
- Wait. What?
- You're seeing someone?
- This is insane.
There is an armed and dangerous
suspect at large.
We gotta focus.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I've been shot at before.
That's not what
I'm talking about.
Something else
is going on here.
and maybe a friendly ear
will help.
Wesley made a deal
with Elijah Stone
to find out where La Fiera
was keeping me in Guatemala.
and now Elijah is
threatening our family.
What do we do?
Thank you. but I'm trying to
figure that out.
Well. it doesn't seem
that complicated.
He's a criminal.
and you're a cop.
There's an element I can't talk about.
but it muddies things.
Well. for what it's worth.
I have never met a couple
so different from each other
and yet so perfect
for one another.
I can't imagine what it is
you're facing.
but I do know this...
The only way you're gonna
get through it is together.
Pull over.
You gonna throw up?
Was that a little
too saccharine?
A little.
but I need to make a call.
I've been known to
keep a secret.
I need to make a call.
and unless you want to
be subpoenaed one day.
you can't hear any of it.
so pull over.
Roger that.
Hey. it's me.
Hey.
Are we okay?
I'm working on it.
I've been digging
into everything
I can find about Elijah.
and I think I have a plan.
We're going to build
a RICO case against him
and make sure
he rots in jail.
which means I need you to
document every interaction
you've ever had
with Elijah...
Every threat
or implied threat.
admission
to his own crimes
or the crimes of
his criminal enterprise.
No. I can't.
That violates
attorney-client privilege.
- Are you serious?
- I know.
He threatened
your wife and baby.
The privilege belongs
to the client.
It's not my privilege
to waive.
You made a vow.
What's more important.
your vow to your client
or to me?
Oh. up on the right...
Silver one.
No. wrong make
and model.
Any other plans
while you're in L.A.?
I have to sell our dad's house.
He hasn't been able to live
on his own for awhile.
Oh. I'm sorry.
Thanks. It's a mess.
It's a lot of work
for one person.
Well. I'm sure
Tim will help.
- What's the point?
- It's a teardown.
Just sell it
and be done with it.
It's got good bones.
We could make some money
if we put in a little effort.
You watch a couple hours of HGTV
and now you're an expert?
Wait. what is
your favorite show?
Mine is "House Hunters
International."
Oh. my God. The best.
Nolan. can you 10-3
to another channel?
Roger that.
Going to 6.
Yeah. look. my sister needs
to sell my dad's house.
but it hasn't been
updated or repaired
since it was built
in 1958.
What are the inspections
gonna reveal?
Uh. 1958?
It's probably got old
cloth-insulated wiring
that would need to
be replaced.
Uh. the plumbing would
need to be updated.
The cast-iron sewer
could be cracked
or rusted through
in places.
and the foundations
would need to be checked.
So it's a teardown.
Oh. no.
not necessarily.
If it has good bones.
some simple repairs
and updates
would double the value
of your house.
I'm happy to swing by.
take a look at it.
see what needs
to be done.
Alright. you will all
have to wait your turn.
Nolan is busy helping me install
my new kitchen backsplash.
Right. but after that.
Kind of regretting
telling everyone
you used to be a contractor.
aren't you?
Hey. Nolan.
do you do pergolas?
'Cause my outdoor space
is really underused.
Landscaping's not really
my area of expertise.
but I have built
a gazebo or two in my day.
Hold on. We just
got sent a location
of one of Marvin Reynolds'
vehicles.
Looks like he's got an RV
that's been collecting
parking tickets
on the 1600 block
of Crenshaw.
We're closest.
We'll... We'll take it.
Heading there now.
Is that from
your lawyer?
Uh. yeah.
It's about
three pages of legalese
that basically comes down to.
I am screwed.
Yeah. but
you're the mom.
I mean.
that has to matter.
Yeah. I'm the mom who all
but abandoned her daughter
when I went undercover
and then nearly got her killed.
Donovan is the one
who was there for her.
Okay. but that
was the past.
Look. I've seen you.
okay?
You're a great mom.
Would a great mom put her kid
through a second custody battle?
I mean. last time
was a nightmare.
She had trouble sleeping.
Her school work suffered.
I just... I don't know
if I can do that again.
- There's our RV.
- Alright.
Be ready to bail in case
he opens fire on us.
Got that.
Yeah. VIN matches.
This is our guy's.
Looks abandoned. but it don't
mean he ain't held up inside.
Alright.
What's the play. Boot?
Well. there's only
one entry point.
so we stay safe
and. uh. try to see
if we can get him to come out
with verbal commands.
And if there's
no response?
Breach?
Or...
Ball-Cam.
360-degree view.
It can even swim.
I am in no mood to play games
with this guy.
We just have to
get it inside.
Man.
This guy
is ready for war.
- So. are we going in?
- Hold on. One sec.
I gotta
check the door.
make sure it's not rigged
with explosives.
Yeah. he definitely
seems like the type.
Alright.
I don't see any wires.
We're all clear.
Alright.
Control. 7-Adam-07.
we're code 4.
RV is unoccupied.
"Rebirth through
the blood of innocents."
Looks like we got ourselves
a manifesto.
Control. Air Three is moving
over to the northeast grid.
Copy. Air Three.
Listen to this...
"Satanic-Hebrew Anglo-Commerce
devoured America."
"The Cabal's slaves
have vanquished us.
Your blood flows
gutter-rivers today."
"The time is at hand
for renewal.
and we will use
the blood of the masters
to wash away
the incestuous sins
of the corrupt
adjudicators."
Barely literate
and yet truly terrifying.
The good news is. we found
the RV with his stash of guns
before he could
get to them.
Even if all he has
is a submachine gun.
we're still looking at a
potential mass-casualty event.
He post anything
to social media?
Nothing new. A dozen older
posts. tilting at windmills.
But he's only got
like 10 followers.
Not sure how wide
his message spread.
Maybe he's using a secret
platform. like 9-Chan?
Forensics is on that.
Got a name
and work address
of a former girlfriend...
Erica Lawrence.
Multiple domestic calls
to her home
when they were together.
Grey wants us
to interview her.
Right.
I think that's her.
Yeah.
That should be her.
Ms. Lawrence?
Yes?
I'm Detective Lopez.
This is Officer Nolan.
Can you tell us the last time
you saw Marvin Reynolds?
What'd he do?
Shot at us.
for starters.
Have you seen him?
Not since last month.
I started dating someone.
and he found out.
I was so careful
about posting anything.
but somehow. he knew.
What happened?
He came over drunk.
He insisted on playing
Russian Roulette.
He said that
if I deserved to live. that...
fate would save me.
H-He pulled the trigger
three times
before my brother came
and scared him off.
I'm so sorry.
And you didn't file
a restraining order?
I was too scared.
I just want him
to forget I exist.
But now. do y...
Do you think that
he would come for me?
We won't let him.
I'll have a unit come
take you to the station
and wait
until we catch him.
Is there anything
you can tell us
that might help us do that?
Um...
He used to boast
that he had weapons
stashed all over the city.
but he never said where.
What was he gonna
use them for?
Killing people.
But I-I don't know
who. exactly.
He wasn't always like this.
When I first met him.
he was intense and a bit quiet.
but he wasn't radicalized.
Well. what changed?
He met this guy online...
Cooper.
He's the one who pulled him
into the Sovereign Citizens.
Any idea where
we can find Cooper?
You know. you'd think
after the seventh time
this guy posted about
overthrowing the government.
someone might have
called us.
Yeah. it's free speech.
so there's not much we can do.
Donovan call you back?
Nope.
Look. I know
you don't want to put Lila
through any more of this
custody stuff.
but you're not the one
who's doing this.
You know that. right?
He is.
He's the one who decided
to move.
Yeah.
But?
I-I mean. who am I
to say that he can't?
E-Especially after
everything that I did.
Okay. you know what?
Maybe I'm wrong.
and maybe I'm bringing
my own experience into this.
but... I still think
you're punishing yourself.
Yeah. like. y-y-you got this
narrative going right now
where he's the saint
and you're some screw-up.
And you know what?
I-I don't know.
I wasn't there.
a-and maybe you were terrible.
But right now.
he's trying to take your kid.
and you're just
letting him do it
because you're so eaten up
with guilt.
Like...
Cooper Sanford?
I'm Detective Lopez.
This is Officer Nolan.
We're looking
for a friend of yours...
Marvin Reynolds.
Doesn't ring a bell.
See. now.
that's a dumb thing to say.
because clearly. it does.
We heard that you sold him
thousands of dollars' worth
of Sovereign Citizen kits.
- And who told you that?
- We're not telling you that.
Yeah. probably
his bitch of a girlfriend.
He dumped her and moved on.
Can't believe anything
that she says.
So you do know him.
I'm gonna need to see
your delegation of authority.
It's right here.
When was the last time you were
in contact with Marvin?
I don't need to answer
any of your questions.
I'm not a citizen
of your corporation.
My corporation?
In 1871.
the United States
stopped being a country
and started being a corporation.
None of the laws passed
since then in any...
Enough of the
Sovereign Citizen crap!
You need to educate yourself!
This "government" that you serve
sells us all into slavery!
Marvin is planning
a terrorist act.
Do you understand that?
If you have
any knowledge of it.
you're an accessory
after the fact.
whether you believe in the law
or not.
I'm not scared of you!
Flat Worms'
"Surreal New Year" plays...
Whoa. whoa. whoa.
I'm gonna cut him off.
♪ Establishing bricks
Clear it out. Go.
Move out.
♪ ...in your hands
Get out!
Let's try this again.
Where's your friend?
What's he got planned?
I do not recognize
your authority.
I do not answer questions.
You will tell me.
or a lot of people will die.
I do not recognize
your authority!
I do not answer questions!
I could change that.
Aah!
Come on!
What are you doing?
I need a lawyer!
See. all these guys
embrace the legal system
when it serves them!
You need to stop now.
Angela.
Out of my way!
Take a step back.
I outrank you.
Take a step back. ma'am.
Aah.
She was trying to hurt me.
No. She was trying to
scare you.
Now. I could charge you
right now with assault...
Yeah. and I could file
a complaint for abuse.
That is a stretch.
Look. I am willing to
uncuff you right now.
We can put this whole thing
in both our rearview mirrors.
but only if you tell me
what Marvin was planning.
Now. believe this...
The detective
was telling the truth.
If Marvin hurts someone
and you're withholding evidence.
you will be charged
right alongside of him.
And good luck
telling the prison guards
you don't believe in
their authority.
I don't know
where Marvin is.
He called me
about an hour ago.
He asked me to meet him.
bring my guns.
I told him I was all talk
and that he was on his own.
What did he say
he needed the guns for?
He just said
it was go time.
And that I'd probably
never see him again.
Maybe I should
just let it go.
but that house
was my childhood home.
I don't want to
tear it down.
I want another family
to live there
and make happy memories.
Of course.
I moved out 10 years ago.
and when I think of home.
I still think of
my parents' house.
What's wrong?
Tim?
Look. I know you don't feel
the same way I do.
but our childhood
wasn't all bad.
Stop.
Alright?
Are you really getting nostalgic
over that place?
What... What do you want?
Some other family
to just cuddle up
under the broken plaster
where dad slammed my head
against the wall?
Dad had a lot of demons.
Dad was a monster.
He's changed.
You haven't seen him
in 20 years.
The only thing
that's changed
is that the drinking
caught up with him.
- Okay?
- He can't throw a punch.
but he's the same guy
underneath.
He's not. and you'd know that
if you'd visit the hospice.
Not in a million years.
Wait. hospice?
I had to move him out of
assisted living last month.
Dad's dying.
I know you and Wesley
are going through a lot
right now.
but that's no excuse.
I wasn't actually
going to hurt him.
It doesn't matter.
We can't play "bad cop"
anymore.
We have to rise above
that way of thinking
because it's corrosive.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Silver Honda...
That could be Marvin's car.
Plate's a match.
That's him.
Control. 7-Adam-15. we have eyes
on Marvin Reynolds' vehicle.
Stand by.
7-Adam-100. 7-Adam-15.
we've cleared the vehicle.
no sign of suspect.
Secure the location
and sit tight
until TID arrives.
Copy that.
Lopez. you see this?
Oil leak.
There was a big vehicle here
parked for some time.
The street cleaners had to
maneuver around it.
Another weapons stash?
So he ditched the Civic
and drove off in an arsenal?
You finally got rid of it.
Rid of what?
That van.
I must've called a hundred times
trying to get it towed.
Well. then. uh. you must
remember some details about it?
Yeah.
Hey. I-I know a great
bereavement counselor.
if you need someone
to talk to.
I have someone. Thanks.
You know. therapy's really
helped me come to terms
with everything that happened
to us when we were kids.
It could help you. too.
I'm good.
You really don't think
you carry some trauma
from what
he put you through?
When you were 7 years old.
he dropped you in Griffith Park
with a compass
and made you
find your way home.
Which I did.
A Tim Test.
A what?
Nothing. Um...
Oh. We got a hit on the van
that Nolan and Lopez I.D.'d.
It's racked up
hundreds of dollars in fines.
Parking tickets?
And tolls.
Where are they clustered?
Uh. they're centered around
the Port of Los Angeles.
Didn't the intel report
state
that Marvin used to work
down there?
Drove a forklift
or something?
Yeah. but he was fired
two years ago.
Why would he
be visiting now?
I'll send some units.
Air Three has eyes
on suspect vehicle.
Northeast corner of lot A.
just off Front Street.
I'm gonna orbit.
Control. 7-Adam-15.
show us responding.
Air Three. 7-Adam-07.
arriving at location.
Stand by.
Air Three. 7-Adam-07.
any movement?
7-Adam-07. I see no movement
in suspect vehicle.
Aaron. relax
and follow my lead.
Front seat clear.
Clear.
Air Three. 7-Adam-07.
no sign of suspect.
but he is
clearly well-armed.
Marvin just posted something
to social media.
History is gonna remember
this day as Sovereigns' Day.
I'm about to light the spark
that's gonna ignite
the revolution.
Maybe we can spot something
that gives away his location.
It's hard to tell.
And who knows
when he recorded that.
I mean. why here?
Uh. there are dozens of targets
at the port.
from the cruise ship terminal
to the port itself.
Yeah. or maybe he's here to kill
the boss that fired him
and pretend
it's for some great cause.
We're taking fire!
We need to back off!
Do you have a location
on the shooter?
Negative. negative.
Where the hell is he?
Air Three.
suspect heading north
along the water.
armed with a long gun.
We're climbing to a safe
altitude. then I'll swing back.
Police. stop!
Control. 7-Adam-07.
alert Long Beach Police.
we are taking fire.
Moving to channel 13
for mutual aid.
Secure that weapon.
We have to stop him before
he gets on that ship.
Clear!
Move! Clear!
Everyone. clear!
What do you got?
Single shooter we've been
tracking since L.A.
- Where is he?
- Somewhere on that boat.
Stay here
in case he doubles back.
Move. move. move!
Come. come.
We should split up.
Covering.
Clear. Clear.
Clear.
Holding.
Go.
Oh.
It's okay.
Stay calm.
Keep going going this way.
exit the ship.
There's other officers
waiting outside.
Exit out that door.
It's a straight shot outside.
okay?
It's clear.
We just came from that way.
Go.
It's all clear.
Clear.
Lopez.
Don't move!
It's okay.
Whoa.
You're safe. you're safe.
Please.
Please get me out of here.
You have to let him go
first.
Okay. I-I'm sorry.
That's alright.
What is that?
You stay here.
You'll be safe. alright?
Please don't leave me!
Just lock the door
behind us.
Hey!
Drop it!
- You're right.
- About what?
I need to fight for Lila.
Even if I lose.
she needs to know
that I would do anything
for her.
You're not gonna lose.
Yeah. I'm not so sure.
I mean. my lawyer is
a lovely person but...
Actually. that might be
the issue.
She's too nice
to be a divorce lawyer.
Well. then hire
someone better... or worse.
Better lawyer.
worse person.
Me and whose paycheck?
Use my lawyer.
She is a shark.
and she owes me one.
The press around my trial
tripled her business.
She'll give you
the friends and family discount.
I'll send you the details.
- Thanks.
- Happy to help.
Chance Peña's "Anxiety
& Mixed Emotions" plays...
- Hey.
- Hm?
Where's Genny?
Oh. she is
calling your nephews.
Um. Tim. listen. uh...
Your sister needs you.
Lucy... I-I realize
that I'm overstepping here.
but just hear me out.
It's clear that
you got the worst of it
with your father.
but she lived through it
with you.
Instead of arguing about
how bad your dad was or wasn't.
maybe as... as children
of abuse.
you would be better off
just supporting each other.
Hey.
You ready to go?
Yeah.
Look. I'm really sorry
about today.
I should've listened more.
I agree.
♪ Tell me that I'm worth it
But thanks for saying it.
That means a lot.
I'm still not going to
see him.
♪ ...I think about
Oh. uh. Nolan.
this is my sister Genny.
Oh! Nice to finally meet you
in person.
I'm so grateful you're willing
to help out with dad's house.
Ah. it's my pleasure.
You know. if you're free
this weekend.
maybe we could go by the place.
see what needs to be done.
and you could give us
an estimate.
Did you just say "we"?
As in you're gonna help?
Well. I checked out some comps
in the neighborhood.
and we can get a million
for that place. easy.
Plus. it shouldn't all
fall on you.
Thanks.
I'll see you both
Saturday.
Nolan.
One second.
Come here.
Hey. can I have
everyone's attention. please?
♪ ...what this world
has for me ♪
♪ Do it all on my own
I would like to formally give
my endorsement for union rep
to a man who has the backs of
every officer in this station...
♪ All on my own
John Nolan.
Et tu. Bradford?
Alright. Nolan.
Good endorsement.
Yeah!
♪ Do it all on my own
Thank you. guys.
Thank you very much.
- Good job. man.
- Great job.
Thank you.
Don't forget to vote.
Don't forget to vote at all.
Thank you.
♪ Ooh. ooh
Is that the solution
to all your problems?
I hope so.
I just hope it's enough
to make the case against Elijah.
Listen.
about today.
don't be too hard
on yourself.
You've been going through a lot
these past few months.
Not an excuse.
I know better.
I'm just glad you were there
to remind me.
What are you doing here?
I'm doing the right thing.
Sergeant Grey came to me
last week. offered his help.
Today. I finally took it.
You told him everything?
Everything.
From the first time I approached
Elijah until today.
How the hell
does that help us?
Because Sergeant Grey
accepted my offer
to be a cooperating witness.
No. you're not doing that.
That will get you
killed.
I've been working all day.
and I think
with a little more digging.
we can hang a RICO case
on Elijah.
But any good lawyer
will swat that away.
He will never see
a jail cell.
Well. you're not
becoming a C.I.
What about attorney-client
privilege?
That could get you
disbarred.
Some things are hard to do.
Some things are scary.
This is both.
but it's something I have to do.
It's not for me. it's for you.
And Jack.
So. look. Angela.
I've already got calls in
to the State's Attorney General
and District Attorney.
They already got a game plan.
and I will personally oversee
how Wesley is utilized.
I promise.
I will do everything humanly
possible to keep him safe.
I need you to tell me
this is okay.
I won't do it
without your support.
We can't screw this up.
Not a single mistake.
Not one.
We won't.
I promise you.
Sync corrections by srjanapala
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm